sanfrancisco.travel 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | San Francisco, CA

**SAN FRANCISCO TRAVEL ASSOCIATION’S PRIVACY POLICY**

Updated: May 24, 2018

Information Collection & Treatment When you use the San Francisco Travel Association’s (“San Francisco Travel”) website, or participate in our sponsored programs, promotions, sweepstakes, games, raffles or contests, we collect information that you submit to us and via “cookies” and other technologies as described below. 

Specifically, San Francisco Travel, its partners and affiliates may collect “personally identifiable information” about you, which means any information that can be used to identify a specific individual, such as name, postal address, telephone, email, zip code, gender and income level. “Personally identifiable information” does not include publicly available information that is lawfully made available to the general public from federal, state, or local government records. The information collected is used for statistical reporting; to determine the effectiveness of the website’s content, programs and advertisements; to “personalize” your experience on San Francisco Travel’s websites, including [http://www.sftravel.com](http://www.sftravel.com/), by providing targeted advertising and/or promotional campaigns; and to contact you or send you promotional materials. We do not collect any personally identifiable information that you do not provide. 

San Francisco Travel also collects “non-personally identifiable information,” which does not reveal your identity, but may be used by us and shared with third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. 

By submitting information to us, you consent to its collection and use by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Users have the option of discontinuing participation in our mailing lists or programs, or editing their personally identifiable information by contacting us. (See “Opt-in/Opt-out,” below.) 

**Registration Information**   
Registration areas on our site may require users to provide personally identifiable information, which is subject to usage as described in “Information Collection & Treatment,” above. 

**Order Information**   
Personally identifiable information provided with a consumer’s order via our online store is subject to usage as described in “Information Collection & Treatment,” above. Financial information provided by the consumer will not be shared, and will be used for the sole purpose of billing the consumer for products purchased from the store. We implement reasonable security measures to protect the financial information you provide to us in conjunction with your purchases from our online store. (See “Security,” below.) 

**Online Survey Information**   
To participate in online surveys, the user may be required to supply personally identifiable information. San Francisco Travel utilizes the information provided subject to usage as described in “Information Collection & Treatment,” above, and to send that user any compensation promised in exchange for completing the survey. 

**Contest/Sweepstakes Information**   
Participation in contests, sweepstakes, raffles, games or similar promotions sponsored by San Francisco Travel or by third parties also requires the disclosure of personally identifiable information. We may share that information with third-party sponsors of the contests, sweepstakes, raffles, games or similar promotions. This information is subject to usage outlined in “Information Collection & Treatment,” above. In addition, you should carefully review the rules of each contest, sweepstakes, raffle, game or similar promotion in which you participate. The extent that the terms and conditions of those rules concerning treatment of your personally identifiable information conflict with this Privacy Policy, the terms and conditions of those rules will control. 

**Cookies and Other Technologies**   
To help us serve you better, we collect non-personally identifiable information, including traffic data and information that identifies your computer or browser. Cookies are pieces of information placed in the settings of your web browser by a website server to identify your computer when you return to a website. Whenever a site welcomes you and tailors data to your specifications, it is reading a cookie left in your browser and identifying information that you may have registered during previous visits, such as your viewing preferences. 

We may use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your status as a participant in our promotions, to tailor information to your preferences, or for other similar purposes. Cookies and other technologies also help us estimate and report the size of our viewing community and traffic. We may also use IP addresses to analyze trends, help us administer the website, track the movement of visitors, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to disable other tracking technologies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features enjoyed by other visitors to our website. 

San Francisco Travel’s website currently does not respond to “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers a choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third party online services. 

**Security**   
We use reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected via our website and under our control so that you can feel comfortable and secure when using the site. A notificatioothern will appear at the lower portion of your browser window when you enter pages on our site secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). We also use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving orders in our online store. Notwithstanding the precautions that we take, we cannot guarantee the security of information that you transmit to us, and shall not be liable for any failure to safeguard your information, whether inadvertent or otherwise. 

**Disclosure for Legal Purposes**   
We may be required to share your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are legally required to do so, or, in good faith believe that we are legally required to do so, we will obey the law. In addition, we reserve the right to use, disclose and share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or as otherwise required by law. 

**Disclaimer Concerning Third Parties**   
We may provide certain personally identifiable information to our partners. Furthermore, we may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include financial institutions, consumer e-mail service providers, web data tracking specialists and reservation booking engines. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

San Francisco Travel’s website contains links to other websites. San Francisco Travel has no control over the content exhibited on these sites, or the administration of them. Use of such sites is subject to each site’s unique privacy policy. 

**Opt-In/Opt-Out**   
You may choose to remove yourself from our mailing list by following the instructions stated on our promotional communications, by completing our online Feedback Form or by sending a request to our Customer Support. (See “Contact Us,” below.) 

**Special Note Concerning Persons Under The Age of 18**  
Our online services are not directed toward persons under the age of 18, and we request that persons under the age of 18 not provide personally identifiable information to us. 

**Contact Us**   
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions, complaints, or if you would like to express a concern, remove yourself from our mailing lists, change your personally identifiable information, or have your personally identifiable information removed from our systems, please contact us by email, phone or mail:   
  
Email: [feedback@sftravel.com](mailto:feedback@sftravel.com)  
Phone: 415-227-2608 By fax at: 415-227-2824   
Mail:   
Privacy Issues  
SF Travel Association  
One Front Street, Suite 2900  
San Francisco, CA 94111  
And if you are a California resident who would like to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information during the preceding calendar year to third parties for their direct marketing purposes (pursuant to California’s Shine the Light law or Civ. Code § 1798.83 et seq.), you may also contact us by mail at the mailing address above.  
  
Please note that any requests to remove your personally identifiable information from our mailing list, or to change your contact information, may take a certain amount of time to process. 

San Francisco Travel is working toward GDPR compliance and will be posting updates to its privacy policy shortly. 

SAN FRANCISCO TRAVEL ASSOCIATION RESERVES THE RIGHT TO UPDATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ITS DISCRETION. ANY CHANGES WILL BE POSTED ON OUR WEBSITE. OUR RIGHT TO USE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WILL BE BASED ON APPLICABLE LAW AND THE PRIVACY POLICY IN EFFECT AT THE TIME THE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED.
